hello everybody and welcome to another
Advanced flipping guide today I'm going
to be showing you probably one of my
favorite and most used flipping
techniques uh some of you probably
already know what I'm talking about but
for those who maybe uh weren't around
when I first started making videos I was
really into decanting potions and uh the
reason this is so profitable is because
you can decant them instantly so what
decanting is if you're not sure is um
taking um
already consumed potions so like say one
dose potions two dose potions and three
dose potions and instantly combining
them into four dose potions there's a
guy in the grand exchange that will do
this for you um the reason this is so
profitable is there often time is a
pretty decent difference between the
relative price of the three dose potion
and the four dose giving you a pretty
good margin uh sometimes a 100 to even
500 GP on each potion um just saying it
now the limit is 2,000
so whatever your margin is just multiply
it by 2,000 that's how much you can
actually expect to make and yeah I'll
show you how you calculate the margin
and then we'll go do some test flips all
right so now I'm going to show you how
you get the margin this is an important
step um but it's actually pretty easy
even though there's a little bit of math
involved so what you're going to do is
you're going to buy and sell a four dose
potion as well as a three dose potion
now um this doesn't have to be done with
the three dose potion but since the
margin is actually shared between the
doses meaning that you'll hit the 2K
buying limit no matter what dose of
potion you're buying at the time it's
mostly cost effective to go with the
three dose
potion so to figure out the margin
you're going to take the price that you
bought the four dose potion at so this
is your finished product what you're
hoping to sell it for and you're going
to multiply that by 75 now you're going
to take off the cost of the three those
potion the price you sold it for when
you're checking it and that is um the
price you're hoping to to obtain the
item set after that that's going to be
your margin so if we take the uh price
we bought the foros potion 1,000
multiply by 75 that'll give us 750 take
off the price of the three dose potion
which would be 600 leaving this with a
150 GP margin and uh if we actually
flipped all 2,000 of those that would
give us 300K so it's really easy to do
very quick especially some of these
cheaper potions like the Super Attack
super strengths really good we'll get
into that in a minute and yeah let's do
some test flips all right so we're going
to do a couple of the decanting flips at
different cash stack amounts uh so one
of the easiest and cheapest is the
energy potion uh so we'll go through a
couple examples here then we'll kind of
speed through it more so to do the uh at
the decanting flip we're going to buy
and sell one of the uh three doses of
the potion so we uh bought it and sold
it then you're going to want to buy the
uh four dose
potion and there we go so we should have
everything for the margin so we'll grab
a calculator open here so we're going to
take the energy potion 4 uh which we uh
bought for 422 times it by 775 and then
we're going to take off um the cost of
the potion which is uh
285 and that leaves us with a 31 GP
margin uh not bad earlier was actually
up to two or 470 so is actually double
that margin uh so we'll definitely go
ahead and uh purchase some energy potion
3es uh we're going to pop them in for
285 and uh 2,000 is the limit for these
types of potions uh so we'll take off a
couple just so um if we do buy all 2,000
that's not going to be hitting the biome
limit we want to recheck it after and
that's going to cost us 571k so not too
bad uh another pretty cheap one is the
Super Attack potion also has a pretty
decent margin on it uh so bought it for
608 and we sold it for
575 and then we're just going to buy the
four do of the
potion okay so now we're going to do the
calculation one more time so $8.49 for
the four dose potion times it by 75 and
then we're going to take off the price
that we're going to buy the Super Attack
3 at so minus 575 and that's a 61 GP
margin so pretty good
uh we'll go ahead and do the super
attack potion 3 honestly guys a lot most
of these potions are profitable it just
kind of depends if you want to invest
the money in it cuz some of them aren't
as profitable as others uh but these two
buy pretty quick so it's not actually a
big issue so now we're going to do a
couple medium cost typing potions uh so
one of the good ones is the super
strength potion so if we do a bit of
math 3688 *
75 so 2766 and then we're going to take
off the super potion 3 - 2501 it's going
to leave us with 265 GP on each potion
time 2,000 so we're slated to make 530k
off this item uh which is awesome
definitely going to do this item so 251
2,000 and this going to run us about 5
mil to do this flip um but we're still
getting 10% back um which is really good
for flipping and uh 252 looks good let's
move on to the next item so another one
that works really well a lot of the time
is the Super energy potion so we'll go
ahead and do the calculation again so
3472 * 75 and then we're going to take
off
2435 and that's going to leave us with
169 GP in profit on each one we're
looking to make 338k on this item that's
great we'll definitely do that so 24 35
2,000 it's going to run us about 5 mil
again and yeah another pretty profitable
item so one thing I was looking at and I
found on G tracker is the agility potion
now if we get it open on GT tracker we
can see that only trades about 4 or 5K a
day so this one is definitely going to
be a much slower buy uh but we'll check
the margin because it could have a very
uh lucrative margin even if uh the the
buying quantity is very low so let's
check that margin that does look pretty
good so
2649 * 75 yeah so 1986 minus what we be
buying them for which would be about
1,600 GP
that is 375 GP on the one item if we did
2,000 of those that would be
750k now it probably take a long time to
buy all these so we're maybe not going
to do uh 2K of these maybe we'll just
try a
thousand uh 16 one
two uh try a thousand of these potions
and uh that's still a really good profit
now it's going to take longer to buy but
it's not that big a deal you can see
some of our other potions are already
coming through already have 71
of the super strength potion 3s I
already have 500 of the energy potions
now maybe the sarad doen Brew now this
is definitely a much more pricey item uh
so this is definitely in the realm of
the more expensive potions you can buy
all right so we have the margin over
here
7265 *
75 and we'll take off
5271 it's going to give us 177 GP on
each one uh now I'm going to do this
it's not as good as the other ones just
because of how much more expensive the
item is um but still a really nice
margin that's going to get
us I don't know 300K or so
340 uh but it is going to run us nearly
10 mil which I probably wouldn't
recommend uh unless you didn't have a
really good option at the time uh now
let's see if we can find any more
potions for the rest of our slots okay
and for the last potion I think we're
going to do is we found the super
restore potion it's a much more
expensive item sometimes it does have a
better margin on it but right now it has
100 GP still going to be a 200k profit
so really nothing to be too unhappy
about uh so we'll buy them for
6415 uh one thing to note is even though
this isn't a good ratio as much as the
other ones uh where they do tend to buy
pretty quickly you can see the S doen
Brews are already half bought exactly
pretty well uh and these are bought as
well all right and last up we're going
to try the zamak Brew I've never used
this item in my life before uh but it
has a uh uh looks like
150 we'll calculate here 214 150 which
is pretty decent and it's not a super
expensive item so we'll go ahead and put
an offer in for as many of these as we
can afford that we have left uh we can
do
1,000
[Music]
and
1.6k all right guys we have a full offer
slot you can see I've been recording for
almost 15 minutes now and they're half
of these are pretty much half done so
it's pretty quick and we'll come back
when these offers have completed all
right guys guys so we pretty much bought
all the potions uh we got 100% of the
agility potions uh 100% of the super
restores uh these ones we I guess H to
limit on all those three uh we didn't
quite buy all of these but I think we're
just going to pull the offers out now uh
cuz we got the majority of them and
that's fine uh so we're going to cancel
these offers out only got about half the
super strength so obviously the margin
changed there uh we got all the super
energies which is nice all right so
we're going to hit collect so we have
all the potions in our inventory and
here is where the easiest thing you're
ever going to do is is uh to decant them
you're just going to run down here to
this guy named Bob right here and you're
just going to hit decant and you can see
bam all the potions have been decanted
into four dose potions as opposed to his
three dose potions so now we have to go
back figure out the prices again just to
make sure that hasn't changed too much
and pop them back in the grand exchange
okay so we did hit the limit on a couple
of the items so I have my secondary
account just to check the prices so the
energy potions are going to be going in
for 421 pretty much just a medium price
here we could probably get more for them
um but let's see we bought all the
energy potions for 570k and we're going
to sell them for 630 that is still a uh
70k profit so pretty good next up the
Super Attack potions buy one more of
those uh see if we can actually buy here
on this account and we can't that's
unfortunate okay so the super attacks
are going to be selling for
824 so overall we're selling them for 1
.23 mil and we bought them for uh 1.15
that's going to be another 80k in profit
there so pretty nice uh looks like we
can sell these super strength potions
for 3650 pretty well uh so we'll pop the
ones we did manage to buy in there
for
3649 uh we bought all the super strength
potions for uh 2 444k and we're selling
for
2678 so that's actually
240k in profit that's really nice from
the super strength potions look we
already sold all the super attacks so
you can see how quickly those actually
sell sometimes all right so we're going
to try selling the uh super energies for
3470 roughly so we're going to sell them
for 5.2 mil almost and we bought the
super energies for 4862 that's a 300K in
profit from the super energies that's
pretty nice so we bought the agility
potion for
2649 uh so we pop those in for
2648 uh so we're selling the agility
potions for almost 2 mil and we bought
them for 1.6 mil so that's 400k in
profit on the agility potions quite nice
I'm kind of interested to see how long
these are going to take to sell uh next
up is the Sarah doen Brew 7805 is what
we can sell it for
7805 it's one of the more pricey items
uh so we're going to sell them all for
10. 420 pretty well anyway that's about
600k in profit almost from that so
that's a really nice margin there
actually next up is going to be the
Super restore so we're buying them for
8564 so we'll sell off the ones we have
for
8563 it's going to be selling for 12.8
mil and we bought them all for uh about
12.8 mil we're actually only going to
get 25k in profit off of this one
unfortunately uh but I can't win on all
of them I guess and last up here is
going to be the zamak Brew uh remember
this one had a pretty decent margin on
it uh we're going to sell it for
3247 and uh we bought them all for 2784
and we're selling them for 3.2 mil
that's another 400c Profit just from the
zamra bru so pretty happy how this went
the only one that really kind of bombed
it was the Super restore and uh that's
only one out of seven or one out of
eight sorry and yeah we'll come back
when these have totally sold all right
guys all the potions have bought um we
only had to repic one of them to sell
and that was a zamra brew uh we only
lost a couple GP on that so not a huge
deal so now we get to see how much money
we actually made from flipping these
potions and I can tell already that we
made quite a bit um so we'll start with
the uh least profitable and go to the
most profitable so the least profitable
was actually the super restores funnily
enough even though it was the most
expensive item it just happened to not
work out uh we only get a 25k profit on
these but still not a loss you rarely
ever lose any money doing this uh next
most profitable item was the energy
potion um and pretty decent for its
price how we bought it for 629k or so we
bought for 570 and we sold it for $629
leaving this with a 60k profit the next
next uh most profitable item was the
Super Attack potion uh we bought them
for $150 and sold them for 1234 that's
going to be 84k in
profit um after that actually the super
strength potion was the next uh most
profitable uh we actually got 234k in
profit on that after that uh the super
energy potion uh we got about
321k on that buying it for 4 862 and
selling it for
5183 um the agility potion I was very
happy with considering we only bought
1,000 uh we got 370k in profit um it did
take a while to buy and sell but not
really actually it took long less time
than the zamak Brew surprisingly um but
again that's 379k in profit there um
afterwards The sidan Brew um very nice
margin on it even though it is an
expensive item this flipped extremely
quickly um if you had 10 Mill spare you
could make an easy 4 500k off this uh we
got 500
64k um actually that was our most
profitable one so we kind of up
at the end uh zamak Brew we ended up
with a 428k profit very happy with that
still and um we'll sell off the random
junk in our inventory and we'll see how
much money we actually made all right so
we sld off all the junk and hit collect
and we'll see how much we actually made
so we're actually over 2 mil in profit
let's see how much more um and how much
we made from just doing this
casually and uh 2 mil and 55k so that is
extremely good now um if you kind of
omitted the most expensive of the items
here the super restore and the sidan
Brew you would have only need half the
amount of money here and you still would
have made 1.5 mil om at those items uh
even more then maybe you would be only
spending 10 mil you may be got 700k in
profit um it's pretty versatile a ton of
different items you can do and you can
do it from pretty low cash stack as low
as prob I recommend at least a mill to
do one of these flips uh anything more
is nice but um yeah very consistent easy
money and I hope you guys enjoyed I will
see you guys in the next video
[Music]